A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Quality Employment Unit, Office Files of Helen Neuborne FA1837
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1974-2015; 1; 15.19 Cubic Feet 40 letter size document boxes.
  - Chauncy Lennon, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Chauncy Lennon - Innovative Strategies for Increasing Self-Sufficiency (ISIS), 2010 (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Chauncy Lennon, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Chauncy Lennon - Council on Foundations, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Chauncy Lennon - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2009 (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Chauncy Lennon - Bridging the Gap initiative, circa 2009 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Direct Care Alliance (DCA), 2009 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Restaurant Opportunities Centers (ROC), 2010 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Ford Foundation Trustees, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - National Council of La Raza (NCLR), 2010 (Box 19, Folder 214)
    The organization National Council of La Raza (NCLR) is now called UnidosUS.
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Grants and travel, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Instituto del Progreso Latino, undated (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - CCC, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Temporary Commission on Day Laborer Job Centers Final Report, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Russell Sage Foundation and Direct Care Alliance (DCA), 2009 (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Workforce Investment Act (WIA), United States Departments of Labor and Education, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Discussions, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 221)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Artineh Havan - Travel, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Artineh Havan - 2010 Fiscal Year budget (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Artineh Havan - 2010 Fiscal Year budget Lines of Work, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Artineh Havan - Quality Employment Active Grants List, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Artineh Havan - Quality Employment unit quarterly GBS, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Artineh Havan - Institute of International Education (IIE), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Artineh Havan - Grantees budgets, circa 2009-2011 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Artineh Havan - Consultants, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Artineh Havan, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Artineh Havan - New budget worksheets, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 232)
  - Artineh Havan - Program unit fiscal budgets, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Artineh Havan - New Grants Administrator, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 234)
    Restricted - Personnel
  - Artineh Havan - Grantee budgets, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Artineh Havan - Budget history, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2009 (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Site questions, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 238)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - Work Supports Initiative Demonstration - Urban Institute calls, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - Medicaid and The Affordable Care Act (ACA), 2010 (Box 20, Folder 241)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation (RWJF), 2007-2010 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - Urban Institute, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - Urban Institute meetings, 2008-2010 (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP), 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - July 21, 2010 memo draft (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - New York City, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - President Barack Obama Administration Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 248)
  - Work Supports Initiative demonstration - United States Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) and Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 249)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 2007-2009 (Box 20, Folder 250)
  - John Colborn Ford Foundation Office of Program Management (OPM) - GBS2, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 251)
  - John Colborn Ford Foundation Office of Program Management (OPM) - Ford Foundation Communication Guidelines Graphic Standards and Style Manual, 2010 February (Box 20, Folder 252)
  - John Colborn Ford Foundation Office of Program Management (OPM) - Tactics and Approaches, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - John Colborn Ford Foundation Office of Program Management (OPM) - Nancy Feller Pre-Grant Inquiry Form, 2010 July 8 (Box 20, Folder 254)
  - John Colborn Ford Foundation Office of Program Management (OPM), 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 255)
  - Quality Employment unit presentations to Ford Foundation Trustees, 2009-2010 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - Living Cities, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 257)
  - MDRC, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - MDRC - Work Advancement and Supports Centers (WASC) Demonstration, 2009-2012 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - United States Department of Labor Women's Bureau Director nominee Sara Manzano-Diaz briefing at the Ford Foundation, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Messaging on tax Issues- Peter Hart, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - MDRC, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 262)
  - MDRC President Gordon Berlin presentation at the Ford Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 263)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) - 2005 State Asset Development Report Card (SADRC) (Box 21, Folder 264)
  - Corporate Voices for Working Families (CVWF), 2009 (Box 21, Folder 265)
  - Corporate Voices for Working Families (CVWF), 2003-2010 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network Meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 267)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 268)
  - Economic Policy Institute (EPI) - State of Working America, 2003-2012 (Box 22, Folder 269)
  - The State of Working America 12th Edition (Box 22, Folder 269)
  - Economic Policy Institute (EPI) - Global workforce development, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 270)
  - Economic Policy Institute (EPI) - Agenda for Shared Prosperity, 2007-2012 (Box 22, Folder 271)
  - Essential Economy Discussion, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 1999-2010 (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Work Life Legacy Award Luncheon, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Work Life Legacy Award, 2005 May 2 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - The Finance Project, 2000-2008 (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - The Finance Project - Employer Involvement in Work Supports, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 276)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) - Annual Budget and Tax Briefing for Grantmakers, Washington D.C., 2009 (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) - 2002 Summer Meeting, Chicago, Illinois (Box 22, Folder 278)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) - Tax strategies, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 279)
  - The Hatcher Group - Waging a Living documentary, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - Progressive States Network, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Public/Private Ventures (P/PV) - Steady Work and Better Jobs guide from MDRC, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Public/Private Ventures (P/PV), undated (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - RealBenefits, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Seedco, 2003-2009 (Box 23, Folder 285-286)
  - Seedco, 2005-2007 (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Seedco, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - Seedco, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 289)
  - Urban Institute, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - OMB Watch - Long-term Proactive Federal Tax and Budget Initiative: National Retreat, Baltimore, Maryland, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 291-292)
  - The middle class, 2011-2012 (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - National Law Employment Project (NELP) - Minimum wage, 2007-2014 (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Demos - Paul Osterman and job quality, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Scheduling - Work flexibility, 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Ford Foundation Consultant - Women's Rights, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - Family Values at Work annual meeting, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - Paid sick days movement - Family Values at Work, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Business leaders - Paid sick days and paid family leave, 2011-2014 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - The What and Why of Narrative: A Powerful Tool for Social Change convening at the Ford Foundation, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Paid sick days, 2010-2013 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Gara LaMarche - States minimum wage, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - White House Summit on Working Families, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - Evaluation stories - Anna Wadia, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Heather Boushey - Center for American Progress (CAP), 2010-2013 (Box 25, Folder 306)
  - 2010 Program Officer orientation, 2009-2011 (Box 25, Folder 307)
  - Grantee related files, 2008-2015 (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - Brookings Institution - Global social contract, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Social mobility, 2012-2014 (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - The Workforce Alliance (TWA), 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Portfolio review, 2008-2013 (Box 25, Folder 312)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Chauncy Lennon evaluation materials, 2009-2014 (Box 25, Folder 313)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Laine Romero-Alston, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 314)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Worker centers, 2010-2013 (Box 25, Folder 315)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Next Generation Workforce Strategies (NGWS) Luis Ubinas budget, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 316)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Labor Innovations for the Twenty-First Century (LIFT) Fund, 2009-2012 (Box 26, Folder 317)
  - Anna Wadia grantee evaluation - Evaluation consultant contracts, 2011-2012 (Box 26, Folder 318)
  - Results reporting - International Labour Organization (ILO), 2010 (Box 26, Folder 319)
  - Results reporting - Hector Cordero-Guzman, 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 320)
  - Results reporting - Anna Wadia evaluation materials, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 321)
  - Results reporting - Assets evaluation, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 322)
  - Results reporting - Quality Employment, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 323)
  - Results reporting, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 324)
  - Results reporting - Workforce and worker centers strategies, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 325)
  - Chauncy Lennon grants - Supports for Low-Income Working Families, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - Chauncy Lennon - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST), 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 327)
  - Chauncy Lennon grants - Work Supports Demonstration Project, 2008-2014 (Box 26, Folder 328-329)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation (AECF) - Behavioral Economics Meeting, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 330)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation (AECF) - Behavioral Economics Meeting, Baltimore, Maryland, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 331)
  - Brookings Institution - Identifying Policies that Would Reduce Poverty, Washington D.C., 2006 (Box 26, Folder 332)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network Meeting, Baltimore, Maryland, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 333)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) Annual Budget Briefing for Grantmakers, Washington D.C., 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 334)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) Annual Budget and Tax Briefing for Grantmakers, Washington D.C., 2012 (Box 27, Folder 335)
  - Assessing the New Federalism Planning Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 336)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) post Hurricane Katrina meeting, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 337)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) Annual Budget Briefing for Grantmakers, Washington D.C., 2005-2008 (Box 27, Folder 338)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) briefing on United States 2006 Midterm Elections, Washington D.C. (Box 27, Folder 339)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) Briefing for Grantmakers, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) Annual Budget Briefing for Grantmakers, Washington D.C., 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 341)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) briefings, 2005-2007 (Box 27, Folder 342)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Meeting, 2004-2007 (Box 27, Folder 343)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Arkansas, 2003-2008 (Box 27, Folder 344)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - California, 2005 January (Box 28, Folder 345)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Connecticut, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 346)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Connecticut Association for Human Services (CAHS) media coverage for Sowing Prosperity, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 347)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Colorado, 2004-2005 (Box 28, Folder 348)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Florida, 2003 May (Box 28, Folder 349)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Georgia, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 350)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Illinois, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 351)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Indiana, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 352)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Kentucky, 2004 October (Box 28, Folder 353)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Maine, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 354)
  - Working Poor Families Project (State indicator reports) - Maryland, 2004-2008 (Box 28, Folder 355)
  - Administration for Children and Families - Implications of Behavioral Research for Social Welfare Research and Policy, Washington D.C., 2010 (Box 28, Folder 356)
  - Administration for Children and Families Office of Planning, Research, and Evaluation (OPRE) - Welfare and Family Self-Sufficiency Research Technical Working Group Meeting, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 357)
  - Yale University economists convening, 2010-2012 (Box 28, Folder 358)
  - Hostos Community College, 2011-2012 (Box 28, Folder 359)
  - Urban Institute, 2008-2012 (Box 28, Folder 360)
  - Center for Working Families (CWF) Leadership Conference, Chicago, Illinois, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 361)
  - University of Chicago School for Social Service Administration Centennial, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 362)
  - Community Service Society - Ending the Safety Net as We Know It? Assessing the Bush Administration's Block Grants Proposals, New York City, New York, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 363)
  - Economic Analysis and Research Network (EARN) Annual Conference, St. Louis, Missouri, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 364)
  - Economic Analysis and Research Network (EARN) Annual Conference, Oakland, California, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 365)
  - Council on Foundations Annual Meeting - Making Poverty History, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 366)
  - National Employment Law Project (NELP) conference on unemployment insurance, Chicago, Illinois, 2004-2006 (Box 29, Folder 367-368)
  - National Governors' Association (NGA) Center for Best Practices and Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP) convening on improving access to work supports, Washington D.C., 2005-2006 (Box 29, Folder 369)
  - Social Justice Infrastructure Funders convening "Conversation on State Infrastructure", 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 2009 (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 1997-2009 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 2004-2009 (Box 30, Folder 373-374)
  - Reflection memos - Workforce development, 2004-2007 (Box 30, Folder 375)
  - Reflection memos - Workforce development, 2002-2007 (Box 30, Folder 376)
  - Women's rights, 1974-1998 (Box 30, Folder 377)
  - Multi-state paid family leave convening, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 378)
  - Working Families Coalition meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 379)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR), 2003 (Box 30, Folder 380)
  - Multi-State Working Families Consortium, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 381)
  - Working Poor Families Project Meeting, Baltimore, Maryland, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 382)
  - Paid Sick Days Summit, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 383)
  - National League of Cities Institute for Youth, Education, and Families, Site Visit and Cross-Site Meeting, San Francisco, California, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 384)
  - Cities Helping Families Build Assets - San Francisco Site Visit and Cross-Site Meeting, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 384)
  - Neighborhood Funders Group (NFG) Annual Conference, Boston, Massachusetts, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 385)
  - Work Advancement and Support Centers (WASC) Cross-Site Meeting, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 386-387)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) - Request for proposals for renewal, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 388)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2008 (Box 31, Folder 389)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) - SWP Meeting, Savannah, Georgia, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 390)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Supporting Work Project (SWP) Meeting, New York City, New York, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 391)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 392)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Budget and grant, 2003-2007 (Box 32, Folder 393-394)
  - Shelley MacDermid, Purdue University - Employee assistance program (EAP) study, 2005-2006 (Box 32, Folder 395)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Center for Workforce Preparation (CWP) grant, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 396)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) Meeting, Savannah, Georgia, 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 397)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 398)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 399)
  - Ford Foundation Report Vol. 32 No. 1, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 400)
  - Program Officer Memo - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), undated (Box 32, Folder 401)
  - Talks to graduate students, 2013-2015 (Box 32, Folder 402)
  - Work Support Strategies (WSS) 2013 Summer Conference, Washington D.C. (Box 32, Folder 403)
  - Jael Silliman Exit Memo - Women's Rights and Gender Justice Portfolio, 2009 March (Box 32, Folder 404)
  - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program initiatives 2012 results status (Box 33, Folder 405)
  - Quality Employment unit portfolio documents, 2009-2011 (Box 33, Folder 406)
  - Ford Foundation Trustees Economic Opportunity and Assets Committee Meeting, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 407)
    File includes a photograph. The photograph shows Helen Neuborne, and a note describes how the photograph was taken during a Learning Breakfast.
  - Ford Foundation Trustees Meetings - Quality Employment unit, 2012-2013 (Box 33, Folder 408)
  - Ford Foundation Trustees Meeting - Role of employers, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 409)
  - Initiative evaluations - Anna Wadia, 2004-2006 (Box 33, Folder 410)
  - Quarterly Strategy Meeting with Luis Ubinas, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 411)
  - Work supports - Wal-Mart meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 412)
  - Work supports - The Conference Board, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 413)
  - Work supports - Chauncy Lennon and low-income fathers and tax credits, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 414)
  - Work supports - Federal stimulus package memos, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 415)
  - Work supports - Work Support Strategies (WSS) 2015 Culminating Conference (Box 33, Folder 416)
  - Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting - Pablo Farias high priority issues, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 417)
  - Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting - Neuborne Quality Employment unit presentation, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 418)
  - Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting - Elizabeth McKeon, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 419)
  - Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 420)
  - Future of Work, 2014-2015 (Box 34, Folder 421)
  - United States Department of Labor meeting with foundations, 2014 (Box 34, Folder 422)
  - Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST) - Post-Election, 2008-2012 (Box 34, Folder 423)
  - White House Summit on Working Families, 2010-2014 (Box 34, Folder 424)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP) - Jared Bernstein, The Full Employment Project, 2014 (Box 34, Folder 425)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) all initiatives, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 426)
  - Family Values at Work convenings, 2009-2012 (Box 34, Folder 427)
  - Communications Consortium Media Center (CCMC) - Polling regarding paid sick days and paid family leave, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 428)
  - Communications Consortium Media Center (CCMC) - Focus Groups, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 429)
  - Communications Consortium Media Center (CCMC), 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 430)
  - Communications Consortium Media Center (CCMC), 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 431)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 432)
  - Lisa Levenstein - Beijing Women's Conference of 1995, 2014 (Box 35, Folder 433)
  - Luis Ubinas, 2008-2009 (Box 35, Folder 434)
  - Grant Actions lists, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 435)
  - Grantmaking strategy, 2007-2010 (Box 35, Folder 436)
  - Notebook - Vice President, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 437)
  - Notebook - Strategy Planning, undated (Box 35, Folder 438)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Ellen Galinsky correspondence, 2008 March 12 (Box 35, Folder 439)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 440)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 441)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Reports, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 442)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Andrew Hahn, Brandeis University and Employee assistance programs (EAPs), 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 443)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Executive Summary, 2006 October 5 (Box 35, Folder 444)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Des Moines, Iowa site visit, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 445)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 446)
  - LifeBridge Guide CD, undated (Box 35, Folder 446)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Savannah, Georgia poverty reduction, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 447)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - Seedco, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 448)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - PathWaysPA, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 449)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - Savannah follow up, 2007 March 12 (Box 36, Folder 450)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - FoodChange, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 451)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - Community Action Project (CAP), 2007 (Box 36, Folder 452)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - Goodwill Industries of San Antonio, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 453)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - Iowa, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 454)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) site visits - New York City, New York, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 455)
  - John Hoffmire, University of Wisconsin-Madison Center on Business and Poverty, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 456)
  - Ellen Galinsky, Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2006 (Box 36, Folder 457)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI)/Center for Workforce Preparation (CWP), 2004-2006 (Box 36, Folder 458)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 459)